Guide to the Hoover Institution Archives Photograph Card Catalog
Hoover Institution Archives
- Marvin Liebman Associates Collection, 200 photographs / 7 envelopes, 1 album (Box 69013 - 10.A.V)
  - 1 album of photographs depicting the fifth conference of the Asian People's Anti-Communist League, Seoul, South Korea, 1959 (Folder fH)
- Linebarger, Paul Myron Anthony Collection, undated; 87 prints / 58 postcards / 2 albums (circa 1931) / 3 recordings / 5 negatives (Box 82115 - 10.A-V, 82115 - 8M.02)
- Linebarger, Paul Myron Wentworth Collection, 110 prints / 1 album / 73 book illustrations / 1 album of newspaper clippings, (1901-1906) (Box 82025 - 10.A-V, 82025 - 8M.02)
- Lindgren-Utsi, Ethel John Collection, August, 1938 (Box 79007 - 10.Map Case, Dr. 2)
  1 oversize photograph depicting the Convention of Anthropology in Copenhagen.
- Litoshenko, Lev N. Collection, 1925 (Box 27002 - 10.A-V)
  2 prints depicting Lev N. Litoshenko, Elena A. Litoshenko, and Josephine Korchinska.
- Littlefield, Marion V. photograph collection, circa 1917-1918; 275 prints / 13 envelopes (Box 47021 - 10.A-V)
  275 prints depicting early aviation in Germany, including World War I. See register for list of photographs.
- Livermore, Edith Collection, 53 prints / 1 envelope (Box 40002 - 10.A-V)
  Photographs relating to activities of the German army during World War I, including scenes of military parades and training exercises in Berlin and of war damage in France. Includes scenes of a 1913 parade in honor of Tsar Nicholas II at Potsdam and a 1914 parade of British troops in London.
- Lodge, John Davis Collection, circa 4442 prints / 7 albums / 121 envelopes (Box 86005 - 10.A-V)
- Loehr, Mrs. Collection, 1917; 7 prints / 1 envelope (Box 67036 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  Depicts street scenes in Petrograd during the Russian Revolution.
- Long (Victor D.) Collection, 3 photos / 1 envelope (Box 75016 - 10.A-V)
  Portrait of Vice Adm. V.D. Long. 1 print. "Signing of Japanese surrender on the U.S.S. Missouri, Spet. 1945," showing Flt. Adm. Chester W. Nimitz, Gen. Douglas MacArthur, Adm. Halsey, Adm. Forrest Sherman, and others. 1 print. "Meeting of U.S. Joint Chiefs of Staff in Wash. D.C., 1943, depicting Flt. Adm. Leahy, Flt. Adm. E.J. King, Comdr. V.D. Long, and others. 1 print.
- Longzinov, V. Collection, 1929; 1 print / 1 envelope (Box XX560 - 10.A-V)
  Photograph of German Russian Children in Kiel, Germany, en route in emigration from Russia to Canada.
- Lopez Frequet (Rufo) Collection, 2 prints / 1 negative / 2 envelopes (Box 65002 - 10.)
  - 1 print and 1 negative depicting Lopez Fresquet and Fidel Castro at the opening of the Sugar Exchange. New York, 1959 (Folder A)
  - 1 print of Fidel Castro and Lopez Fresquet, undated (Folder mB)
- Loucheur (Louis) collection, 1977; 11 photos / 1 envelope (Box 61001 - 10.A-V)
  11 photos depicting Louis Loucheur, French industrialist and Minister of Commerce, and/or Aristide Briand and others. Received trough J. de Launay.
- Lovestone, Jay Collection, circa 760 prints, 42 postcards, 12 negatives, 3 slides / 49 envelopes (Box 75091 - 10.A-V)
- Lowdermilk (Walter C.) Collection (Box 70049 - 9.13)
  - 19 prints of the Sabo Works in Japan, undated (Folder A)
  - 55 prints dealing with agriculture, soil erosion and conservation in the Far East, undated (Folder B, C)
- Lowman, Myers G. Collection, 11 envelopes (Box 67019 - 10.A-V)
- Lukomskii (Aleksandr S.) Collection, 1924; 1 print / 1 envelope (Box 75008 - 8.37)
  1 photograph depicting baron-General Petr Nikolaevich Wrangel.
- Lundeen, Ernest Collection, 1363 prints, 6 negatives, 21 duplicates, 48 postcards / 42 envelopes, 2 albums (Box 50003 - Photo file)
- Lutz (Ralph H.) Collection, 2 prints / 2 envelopes (Box 68039 - 10.A-V)
  - 1 photo of Ralph H. Lutz, undated (Folder m)
  - 1 group photo of fraternity members including R.H. Lutz, April 1, 1948
- Luxemburg, Rosa Collection (Box 39000 - 10.A-V)
  - 2 prints of Luxemburg attired in Japanese kimono, 5 postcards of Luxemburg's profile, undated (Folder A)
  - 3 postcards of demonstration in Munich and 5 prints of Luxemburg and Liebknecht's grave site, February 16, 1919 (Box B)
  - 3 postcards and 2 prints of Karl Liebknecht throughout his life. print of Wilhelm Liebknecht's grave site (Karl Liebknecht's father), undated (Folder C)
  - 2 prints of Leo Jogisches, undated (Box D)
- Harold F. Lynn Collection, 1943-1945; 5 photo albums (Box f63018 - 10.A-V Album fA-E)
  Photographs depicting activities of the 93rd U.S. Naval Construction Battalion in the Pacific theater during World War II.
- Lyons, Eugene Collection, 641 prints / 10 envelopes /2 albums (Box 85006 - 10.A-V)
  - 91 prints depicting E. Lyons at various stages of his life, undated (Folder A-C)
  - 6 prints of E. Lyons and his wife, Billy, undated (Box D)
  - 30 prints of the Lyons family and friends, undated (Box E)
  - 12 prints depicting E. Lyons at various speaking engagements, undated (Box F)
  - 14 prints depicting E. Lyons with individuals and groups, undated (Box G)
  - 6 prints of E. Lyons' books on display, undated (Box H)
  - 10 prints of various individuals and groups, undated (Box I)
  - 6 prints of David Sarnoff, undated (Box J)
  - 118 prints of E. Lyons with the Zellerbach Commission on the European Refugee Situation tour of Europe, October 15 - November 1, 1957 (Folder fK)
  - 348 prints of E. Lyons, his wife and family, and others, 1920-1980 (Folder fL)
- McAllister, Bruce R. Collection, 1959; 36 prints / 1 envelope (Box 82048 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  Depicts French soldiers in West Berlin, and street scenes in East Berlin. Published in the "Harvard Alumni Bulletin"
- MacArthur, Douglas (General) Collection, undated; 1 print / 1 envelope (Box 42006 - 10.A-V)
  1 print with Maj. Gen. Richard K. Sutherland. Autographed by both.
- Macarthur, Douglas (General) Collection, Spring, 1946; 1 print / 1 envelope (Box 46008 - 10.A-V)
  1 print taken at the honor guard review in front of the American Embassy, Tokyo.
- McCann, Robert Ezra Collection, undated; 324 slides / 16 slide boxes (Box 76040 - Slide Cabinet)
  324 slides, depicting Beijing in the first half of the 20th century
- McCutcheon, John Tinney Collection, 1903-1944; 25 cartoons (Box 80190 - Map cabinet)
  Relate to world politics and U.S. Foreign relations.
- McDonald, John, (Collector) Collection, undated (Box 86062 - 10.A-V)
  - 1 print of Karl Marx; 1 print of Mikhail Borodin; 1 print of Chen Shu-jen; 1 print of Li Fu-lin; 1 print of T.V. Soong; 1 print of Chu Pei-te; 1 print of Tan Yen-k'ai; 1 print of Liao Chung-k'ai; 1 print of Pai Wen-wei; 1 print of Teng Tze-chih; 1 print of Sun of, undated (Folder A)
  - 1 print of Sun Yat-sen; 1 print of Ku Ying-fen; 1 print of Semenov, G.M.; 1 print of Wu Ch'ao-shu; 1 print of Wu T'ieh-cheng; 1 print of Wu T'ing-fang; 1 print of V.I. Lenin; 1 print of the Tomb for the 72 martyrs (Chinese revolution, 1911); 1 print of Ch'eng ch'ien; 1 print of Huang Chin-yuan; 1 print of Sun Yat-sen and associates, undated (Box B)
- McDonnell, (Geoffrey) Collection, 1918-1919; 175 photos / 1 photo album (Box XX233 - 10.A-V Album f)
  1 album of 175 photos, relating to the activities of the Canadian and other Allied expeditionary forces in Siberia, including some correspondence and memorabilia, compiled by a Canadian officer Lt. Col. Geoffrey McDonnell.
- McLean, Katherine S. Collection, 1918-1920; 24 prints, 2 post cards / 1 envelope (Box 42014 - 10.A-V)
  Photographs and post cards of Y.W.C.A workers and American soldiers at Camp Fremont and Camp Kearny, California, and of Czechoslovakian soldiers evacuated to these camps from Siberia.
- McMullin (Dare Stark) Collection, 101 prints / 7 envelopes / 1 print in map cab. (Box XX205 - 10.A-V)
  - 23 photos of Mr. and Mrs. Herbert Hoover, undated (Folder A, mA, m*A)
  - 23 photos depicting the President's Camp at the Rapidan (interior and exterior), undated (Box B)
  - 3 photos of Mr. Hoover associates and/or White House Aides, undated (Folder C, mC)
  - 52 photos depicting the White House interior during H. Hoover's presidency, 1929-1933 (Box D)
- Machlup, Fritz Collection, 115 prints / 6 envelopes, 1 album box (Box 83037 - Photo file, 8M.02)
  - 1 print, depicting Fritz Machlup, and 4 prints with or of Herma Gelles, 1947-1951 (Folder A)
  - 3 prints depicting participants of the Economics-in-action program at the Case Western Reserve University, Cleveland, Ohio, including 1 with Fritz Machlup, 1966 (Box B)
  - 1 album of 6 prints depicting Fritz Machlup receiving an honorary degree at the Case Institute of Technology, Cleveland, Ohio, 1967 June 13; and 2 albums of 76 prints depicting Fritz Machlup and others at the 4th World Congress of Economists, Budapest, Hungary, 1974 August 19-24 (Folder fC)
  - 5 prints depicting Fritz Machlup receiving an honorary degree at the University of Vienna and others in the audience, 1971 June 17 (Box D)
  - 7 prints, including 4 duplicates, depicting Friedrich A. von Hayek, undated (Box E)
  - 2 prints, depicting Ludwig von Mises, undated (Box F)
  - 10 prints and postcards, depicting Eugen Bohm-Bawerk, Friedrich List, Alfred Marshall, John Stuart Mill, David Ricardo, Henry C. Simons, Adam Smith, and Friedrich von Wieser, undated (Box G)
- Magistretti, William L. Collection, 56 slides / 3 boxes in 1 envelope (Box 79088 - 10.A-V)
  Depicts the funeral in Moscow in 1953 of Lev Mekhlis, Soviet Commissar of State Control, 1940-1941 and 1945-1950, and Deputy Commissar of Defense, 1937-1940 and 1941-1942.
- Makerere University Collection, 1969; 107 slides / 4 boxes (Box 72041 - Slide Cabinet Box A-D)
  Slides prepared by the Department of Religious Studies and Audio-Visual Center of Makerere University, Kampala, Uganda, illustrating the history of Christianity in East Africa. Inventory.
- Malek, Frederic V. Collection, 1972-1973; 4 prints, 2 proof sheets / 1 envelope (Box 84009 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  3 prints and one proof sheet of a swearing-in ceremony, with Frank Zarb, Frederic Malek, and others; one print and one proof sheet of Frederick Malek.
- Marmon, (Howard C.) Collection, undated; 83 prints / 2 envelopes / 7 photo albums (Box 60001 - 10.A-V)
  - 75 photos of aero planes, aviators, and aerial views from Italy, W.W. I, undated (Folder A)
  - 8 photos of aviators, and aerial views with maps from Italy, W.W. I, undated (Folder mB dr.5)
- Marshall, Stewart M. Collection, undated; circa 300 slides / 2 drawers (Box 79074 - 10.03)
  Depicts World War I scenes in France, scenes of engineering construction in India and the Soviet Union, and Stanford University.
- Marshall (William J.) Collection, 202 prints / 16 negatives / 6 envelopes (Box 81061 - 10.A-V)
  - 72 prints of William J. Marshall and family; unidentified individuals' Naval functions; and European and Far Eastern landscapes, circa 1945-65 (Folder A-mC)
  - 48 prints and 16 negatives of Naval functions; unidentified individuals' Italian and Mediterranean landscapes, all relating to the European tour of the U.S.S. Spokane, 1949 (Box D)
  - 39 prints depicting battle scened of the Normandy Invasion, June, 1944 (Box E)
  - 43 prints depicting William J. Marshall, American Admirals William Fechteler and Robert Carney, Italian Admiral Emilio Ferreri, other, unidentified individuals, cultural sights, and senic views from when Campatin Marshall was U.S. Naval Attache at the U.S. Embassy in Rome, Italy, circa 1951-1952 (Box F)
- Maryhill Museum, Maryhill, Washington Collection, undated; 6 prints / 1 envelope (Box 79091 - 10.A-V)
  Depicts furniture and souvenirs donated to the Maryhill Museum by Queen Marie of Romania.
- Masland, John W. Collection, May 1, 1946; 32 photographs / 1 envelope (Box 45005 - 10.A-V)
  Photographs of May Day demonstrations in Tokyo, Japan.
- Mason, Frank E. Collection, undated; 164 prints and post cards / 7 envelopes (Box XX007 - 10.A-V)
  - 36 post cards and prints of Adolf Hitler, undated (Folder A)
  - 8 post cards of Adolf Hitler, Erich Ludendorff and other defendants at the Munich Putsch trial, 1923-24 (Box B)
  - 8 post cards depicting Chancellor Wilhelm Cuno and leading Nazis, including Josef Bauer, Arthur Dinter, Hermann Esser, Gottfried Feder and Julius Streicher, undated (Folder C)
  - 72 post cards and prints of members of the Nazi party and of Nazi party rallies and parades, undated (Box D)
  - 24 post cards of Nazi party headquarters at the Braune Haus, Munich, undated (Box E)
  - 3 post cards of the funeral of Empress Victoria of Germany, 1901 (Box F)
  - 13 prints of the removal of archival material from the Nazi House of the Press, Berlin, to be sent to the Hoover Institution, 1945 (Box G)
- Mason (James B.) Collection, 1943-45; 34 prints / 1 envelope (Box XX161 -10.)
  34 prints depicting scenes of the activities of the Medical Service Advance Section Communication Zone of the European Theater of Operations, including air evacuations, hospitals, supply depots, and charts of general medical operations and needs. Belgium, France.
- Mathews (Sarah E.) Collection, 57 photos / 1 envelope, 231 photos; 1 album (Box 71055 - 10 A-V)
  - 57 photos of activities of the American Red Cross and the American Expeditionary Forces in Siberia (Vladivostok), circa 1918-20 (Folder A)
    Includes photo of General William S. Graves and Grigorii M. Semenov.
  - 231 photos in one album relating to the American Red Cross and the A.E.F. in Siberia, circa 1918-20 (Folder fB)
- Mattusch, Kurt Robert Collection, 21 prints / 1 envelope (Box 81096 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  21 prints depicting conditions of cattle breeding in India; Korean military men and politicians, including Prime Minister, General Yo Chan Song, and American specialists in Korea in 1960s; Mattusch, Kurt Robert and his relatives and good friends; and National Socialist anti-semitic cartoon.
- Maurin, Joaquin Collection, undated; 46 print and postcards / 3 envelopes (Box 77021 - 10.A-V)
  - 26 prints and postcards depicting scenes from the Spanish political scene of the 1920s and 1930s as well as of Spanish communist leaders and friends of Maurin active in his part, including Jose Capdevilla, Rafael Campalans, Horacio Echevarrieta, Julian Gorkin, Manuel Grossi-Mier, Jose Carlos Mariategui, Joaquin Maurin, Andres Nin, Facundo Perezagua, Luis Portela, Tirella, undated (Folder A)
    Includes a few photographs of the delegates to congresses of the Communist International.
  - 13 prints and postcards depicting Communist leaders from various countries, including August Bebel, Nadezhda Konstantinovna Krupskaya, Jim Larkin, Vladimir Ill'ich Lenin, Rosa Luxemburg, Bertram D. Wolfe, undated (Box B)
  - 7 prints depicting Spanish and Latin American artists, intellectuals and politicians, including Jaime Benitez and his wife, Pablo Casal and his wife, Juan Ramon Jimenez, Alfonso Reyes, Eduardo Santo, Ramon Sender, undated (Folder C)
- Meader (A.) Collection, undated (Box 74073 - 10.A-V)
  4 photos. (one of Mrs. A. Meader with her father and daughter; one of her home; and two of Mrs. A. Meader as Mary Stuart.
- Meese, Edwin III Collection, 2 prints (Box 90010 - 10.A-V)
  - 1 print of Edwin Meese III at Lake Merritt Breakfast Club, Oakland, California, Dec. 10, 1981 (Folder A)
  - 1 print of Edwin Meese III at National Judicial College, Reno, Nevada, Oct. 22, 1982
- Metcalfe (John C.) Collection, 5 envelopes / 82 prints and 10 negatives (Box 72069 - 10 A-V)
  - 57 photos of German-American Bund activities, 1937 (Folder A-B)
    Includes photos of Fritz Kuhn, Karl Weiler, Herman Schwinn, John C. Metcalfe, and others.
  - 15 photos of Christian Nationalist Party activities including Party convention appearances of Daniel Kurtz, Gerld L. K. Smith, and Maj. Gen. George Van Horn Moseley, 1945-49 (Folder C)
  - 14 photos of Nazi organizers in South America including Hans Niroun, Adolf Keim, Paul Tegeler, and others, undated (Box D)
  - 6 photos of the German-American Bund convention in New York City, and of a display of German-American publications, July, 1937 (Folder E, m)
- Miles, Milton E. Collection, undated; 35 photos / 1 negative / 4 envelopes (Box 68028 - 10.A-V)
  - 1 group photo of the Inter-American Defense Board, July, 1951, with a list of members attached; 1 photo of M. E. Miles with President Galo Plaza lasso of Ecuador at the Mark Hopkins Hotel, San Francisco, 1951. 1 photo of M. E. Miles with Captain D'Ambrosio and Admiral Aqwar of the Argentine Navy and Colonel Porch of the U.S. Army, circa early 1950s; 3 photos of the body of Gilmer Fisher, killed in the "Campeche Affair" in Mexico in 1953, with a letter from Abraham Katz, American Vice Consul, Merida, Yucatan, Mexico, attached. 8 photos of M. E. Miles with Venezuelan naval officers during a visit to Puerto Cabello, Venezuela, circa June, 1951, with notes from Captain Oscar Ghersy Gomez and Commander Wolfgang Larrazabal attached (Folder A)
  - 4 photos of Chinese junks flying American flags, circa 1945; 1 photo of M. E. Miles with Admiral Charles M. Cooke, Jr., and Commander Ed Burroughs, undated. 1 photo of M. E. Miles visiting Chiang Kai-shek in Chungking, China, circa April-May, 1942 (Box B)
  - 1 photo of M. E. Miles riding in a helicopter from the U. S. S. Worcester, undated; 1 photo of Queen Fredericka of Greece and Admiral T. S. Combs during a royal visit aboard the U. S. S. DesMoines, November 3, 1949 (Folder C)
  - 8 photos of M. E. Miles during a visit to the Naval Petroleum Reserve No. 4, Point Barrow, Alaska, January, 1952; 3 photos of the Permanent Joint Board on Defense (Canada-U.S.), circa 1951-1952; 1 photo of M. E. Milesbeing welcomed to Miramare Castle, Trieste, 1948;; 1 negative of a $20,000 check payable to M. E. miles, March 18, 1942 (Box D)
- Miller, Bernice Collection, 200 prints, 1 album / 5 envelopes (Box 53001 - 10.A-V)
  - Album of photographs of Herbert Hoover, Bernice Miller, and others at a party of the Key Largo Anglers Club, 1962 (Folder A)
  - 3 prints of Herbert Hoover (1 autographed), and 1 print of Richard Nixon and three astronauts (autographed by Nixon and the astronauts), undated (Folder mB)
  - circa 200 prints of Herbert Hoover and associates, 1956-1964 (Folder C-E)
- Miller, Evgenii Collection, 73 prints, 7 glass negatives / 17 envelopes, 1 album, 1 box. (Box 28007 - Photo file)
- Miller (IVA M.) Collection, 90 prints / 1 envelope (Box 72061 - 10 A-V)
  90 photographs of daily life in China and of hospital scenes in the Isabella Fisher Hospital, Tientsin, China, circa 1910-30. Collected by Dr. I. M. Miller as medical director of Fisher Hospital. Gift of Ethel A. Miller, 1972.
- Miller, Krzysztof Collection, undated; 39 prints / 3 envelopes (Box 93026 - 10.A-V Envelope A-B, mC)
  39 prints depicting conditions in concentration camps in Bosnia during the Yugoslav civil war.
- Miller, William P. Collection, 1326 prints / 15 envelopes, 5 16mm. films, 1 album / 1 oversize box, 3 framed documents, 2 framed photographs (Box 77074 - 10.A-V, 77074 - 8M.02, 77074 - 8M.FC)
  - 132 prints of Germany, Austria, France, primarily U.S. Signal Corps photos, April-May 1945 (Folder A)
  - 77 prints of Germany, Austria, France, primarily U.S. Signal Corps photos, April-May, 1945 (Box B)
  - 74 prints of Germany, Austria, France, primarily U.S. Signal Corps photos, April-May 1945 (Folder C)
  - 65 prints of Germany, Austria, France primarily U.S. Signal Corps photos, April-May 1945 (Box D)
  - 74 prints of Germany, Austria, France primarily U.S. Signal Corps photos, April-May 1945 (Box E)
  - 93 prints of Germany, Austria, France primarily U.S. Signal Corps photos, April-May 1945 (Box F)
  - 142 prints of North Africa, 1943 (Box G)
  - 58 prints of North Africa, 1943; 15 unidentified people; 34 prints of Germany, 1945; 11 postcards of Germany (5 of Berchtesgaden), undated (Box H)
  - 89 prints of Austria, Germany, Italy, primarily U.S. Signal Corps photos, April-May, 1945 (Box I)
  - 97 prints of North Africa, circa 1943. 5 prints of William P. Miller; 2 prints of William Miller with others; 3 prints of unidentified people; 4 prints of General Mark W. Clark with others (Box J)
  - 10 prints of William P. Miller; 12 prints of William Miller and others; 10 prints of scenes in Germany (?), 2 prints of Brigadier General G.F. Wooley; 2 miscellaneous prints, undated (Box K)
  - 5 prints of Heinrich Himmler's summer home on the Tegern Sea, Germany, 1945; 1 print of Wernher von Braun and Megnus von Braun surrendering to American troops, Reutte, Austria, 1945; 3 prints of Brigadier General Carl A. Baehr receiving the Croix de Guerre from General Lattre de Tassigny; 1 print of Edouard Daladier and jean Daladier; 1 print of General Maxime Weygand, Lt. General Alexander M. Patch, Jr., General Maurice Gamelin; 1 print of Edouard Daladier, lt. General Alexander M. Patch, Jr., and Paul Reynaud; 1 print of Lt. General Alexander M. Patch, Jr. and Paul Reynaud; 1 print of Maurice Gamelin, Edouard Daladier, and Payl Reynaud; 1 print of Lt. General Alexander M. Patch, Jr. and Maruice Gamelin; 1 print of Lt. General Alexander M. Patch, Jr. with others; 1 print of Jefferson Coffrey and Lt. General Alexander M. Patch, Jr.; 65 prints of Germany, Austria, France, 1945 (Box L)
  - 71 prints of Italy, Germany, Austria, 1945; 7 prints of Congressional group's visit to Germany, 1945 (prints include Rep. Edward Izac, Sen. Everett Saltonstall, Rep. Dewey Short, Rep. James W. Mott, Maj. Gen. Lowell W. Rooks, Lt. General Alexander M. Patch, Jr.; 1 print of Polish General Komoruski Bor; 1 print of Francois Comte de la Roque; 1 print of Maj. General Anthony M. McAuliffe and gen. Maxime Weygand; 1 print of Gen. Komoruski Bor and others; 1 print of Maj. General Anthony M. McAuliffe and Edouard Daladier; 1 print of Paul Reynaud; 1 print of Paul Reynaud, maj. Gen. Anthony M. McAuliffe, Gen. and Mme. Maxime Weygand, Gen. Maurice Gamelin, and Edouard Daladier; 1 print of General Komoruski Bor and others (Box M)
  - 60 prints of Germany and Austria, 1945; 1 print of Lt. Gen. Alexander M. Patch, Jr. and Gen. Jean de Lattre de Tassigny; 1 print of Maj. Gen. J.T. Lewis, Lt. Gen. Alexander M. Patch, and Gen. Jean de Lattre de Tassigny; 1 print of Undersecretary of War Robert P. Patterson, Lt. Gen. Alexander M. Patch, Jr., and Lt. Gen. Wade H. Haislip; 1 print of Patterson and Lt. Gen. Wade Haislip; 1 print of Lt. John G. Winant (son of U.S. Ambassador to Great Britain); 1 print of Lt. Gen. Alexander M. Patch, Jr., King Leopold III of Belgium and Princess de Rethy (wife of King Leopold), Lt. Gen. Wade Haislip; King Leopold III of Belgium, Lt. Gen. Wade Haislip, and Lt. Gen. Alexander M. Patch, Jr.; 4 prints of Under-secretary of War Robert R. Patterson, Lt. Gen. Alexander M. Patch, Jr., and Brig. Gen. Patrick H. Tansey; 7 prints of American Ambassador to France Jefferson Coffrey's visit to Dachau, 1945 (Folder N)
  - 9 negatives, undated (Folder O)
  - 1 album of prints of World War in Germany and France, 1939-1945 (Folder fP)
  - 1 film North Africa, 1942-1943; 1 film North Africa, circa 1943; 1 film North Africa, Italy, France, World War II; 1 film, Germany, circa 1945. 1 film, Germany, Austria, 1945 (Folder FC)
- Milton, Harry Collection, undated; 6 prints / 1 envelope (Box 87010 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  Depicts members of the Partido Obrero de Unificacion Marxista (POUM) militia, including a contingent from the Independent Labour Party of Great Britain, during the Spanish Civil War and Harry Milton in uniform in 1945 and in the 1980's.
- Miroliubov (Nikander I.) Collection, undated; 1 print / 1 envelope (Box 36007 - 8M.19)
  1 photograph of Nikander I. Miroliubov.
- Mirovicz (Maj. Gen.) Collection, 1915-16; 5 prints / 1 envelope (Box XX125 - 8.22, 10AV)
  5 prints depicting the terrain of military operations of the Second Rifle Brigade in battles on Riga Front and in the Carpathian Mountains. Aerial Photographs. Prints are labeled in Russian with English translations